(Sheldon:)If I were to give you this gift basket...
(Sheldon:)...based on that action alone
and no other data...
(Sheldon:)...infer and describe the hypothetical
relationship that exists between us.
(Assistant:)Excuse me?
(Leonard:)Here.
(Sheldon:)Now are we friends? Colleagues? Lovers?
(Sheldon:)Are you my grandmother?
(Assistant:)I don't understand
what you're talking about...
(Assistant:)...and you're making me
a little uncomfortable.
(Howard:)See? Sounds just like you and Penny.
We'll take it.
(David:)Hey, Leonard. Come, join us.
(Leonard:)Oh, hey, Dave. And Penny.
What a surprise.
Hey, Leonard. Dave was showing me
around the university.
(Penny:)You know, this place is unbelievable.
(Leonard:)Yeah, I know. I've been offering
to show you around for a year and a half.
(Leonard:)You always said you had yoga.
- I never said that.
- Maybe I heard you wrong.
A lot of words sound like "yoga."